07815 836996 adamhills91@gmail.com www.adamhills.me

PROFILE

SKILLS

Web developer with experience in building responsive and user-friendly web pages and applications. These skills have been acquired alongside working a full-time hospitality management position, and I am now determined to join an experienced team to focus and build on my future in web development.

ORILLO		
• HTML	• CSS	JavaScript + ES6
• PHP	• Git	• React
EDUCATION ———		

The Complete Web Developer: Zero to Mastery - Udemy, by Andrei Neagoie

Online course that teaches modern Web Development fundamentals and the skills required to become a full stack developer. This course covers:

- HTML5, CSS and JavaScript from the ground up
- Frameworks including Bootstrap and React.js
- The command line and Git/GitHub

freeCodeCamp

Completed the following modules:

- Responsive Web Design Media queries, Flexbox and CSS Grid, as well as HTML and CSS fundamentals
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures includes ES6
- Front End Libraries covers Bootstrap, jQuery and React

Audio and Music Technology BSc

First Class Honours

- First Class grade in Web Development Module projects included designing and coding two websites from a brief using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.
- First Class grade in Programming for Audio Module projects included programming plugins and virtual instruments using C++ and Max/MSP.

University of the West of England, Bristol 2011 - 2014

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Starbucks
Store Manager
July 2018 – present

Responsible for overseeing the daily operations of the store by leading and mentoring the sales team via clear communication and by example. Recruiting and training suitable members of staff. Maintaining 15%+ nett sales growth per year.

Royal Caribbean Cruise Lines Youth Staff Feb 2016 - 2018 Responsible for delivering a range of high energy activities for children on board some of the biggest cruise ships in the world, as well as hosting sports and gaming activities for the teenagers. Building rapport with guests, both parents and their children.

Camp America
Camp Counsellor
Jun 2014 – Sep 2015

Responsible for delivering a range of activities for children at a summer camp in Florida, USA, including sports, arts and crafts, games, music and swimming.